The final exercise per se is really about trying to put all of this together.
And so this time, you're not going to have the base.
What we're going to do is we're going to create an edit page.
Because right now, you have the ability to delete something,
but you don't have the ability to modify an existing type.
And so this is going to come like, this will kind of stretch some people in this regard.
So let me actually go ahead and do something real quick.
Let me get never mind.
In case I actually anyone asked me about that,
I have an alias inside of my terminal,
because I decided that get reset dash dash,
off head till day one was too much to type.
So get never mind is my way of just saying that,
I don't want the last one, so get rid of it for me.
So let me just drop that and then check out get push origin main force.
OK, now that should be gone.
All right, so we're going to check out 11 begin.
And so just to give you just a little bit of a scaffold,
what we're going to do, check out 11 exercise,
is we're going to go inside the dishes page,
because that's where you all have been working anyways.
And then actually, we're going to wait any of the dish card.
And the dish card is going to get another button called edit dish.
And so this will be this will be broken just so you know, when you get this.
So let's make it a yellow button is warning and let's say edit.
And in fact, you know what, I'll leave you to hook it up yourself.
And then edit, there you go.
And so when you click on this, what I want you to do is either up to you,
you can create a brand new page where the router will grab it,
and then you can use your store to fetch the thing, type everything.
Let's see where you can get to in the next 15 minutes.